Dice Privacy Policy
===================

###### Last Updated: 10/01/2024

Dice.com and DHI Group, Inc. are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing personalized career management services on our websites and applications. This Privacy Policy for Dice.com describes our practices on the collection, use and disclosure of your information in connection with our parent entity, DHI Group, Inc., and subsidiaries and affiliates acting on our behalf (collectively, "Dice").

**California Notice At Collection**

If you are a California resident, this Privacy Policy contains information that we provide pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 as amended from time to time (“CCPA”). That section includes information regarding the [categories of information to be collected](#CAPersonalInfoCategories), the [purposes](#CAPurposesforUsingorDisclosing) for which the categories of information are collected or used, whether the information is [sold or shared](#CaCoCtSoldorShared) and how to [opt-out,](#CARighttoOptOut) and how long the information is [retained](#RetentionofPI). You can find those details by clicking on the above links

**Overview**

Note: Any reference to "we", "us", "our Site" or Dice are references to the [www.dice.com](https://www.dice.com/) site (the "Site"). Dice provides links to the websites of many other companies to which this policy does not apply.

We at Dice are committed to good privacy practices regarding your personally identifiable information. Your loyalty as a job seeker, customer or visitor is important, and we hope that our concerns regarding your privacy, as described in this policy (the "Privacy Policy" or "Policy"), demonstrate our commitment to making your experience with Dice an enjoyable and satisfying one.

The data controller of DHI and its subsidiaries' websites is located at 5745 Raccoon River Drive, Suite 200, West Des Moines, IA 50266. Adam Stokes is the data protection officer and can be contacted at [DPO@dice.com](mailto:DPO@dice.com?subject=DPO%20Contact) or by mail at Adam Stokes (DPO), DHI Group Inc, 5745 Raccoon River Drive, Suite 200, West Des Moines, IA 50266.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by the websites and mobile application that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively the "Sites").  The Privacy Policy governs your interaction with the Sites and your registration for and use of our online services (collectively, the "Services"). This Privacy Policy also does not apply to information we collect about Dice employees, contractors, or as emergency contacts, beneficiaries, or dependents of Dice’s employees or contractors. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use Agreement and other published guidelines, we do not release personal information about our users and visitors without their permission. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the entire Privacy Policy. Please click on any of the links below to review that particular section.

[H. Data Subject Rights and Correction of Personal Information](https://www.dice.com/about/privacy-policy#section-h)  

**A. The information we gather**

###### Personal Information You Provide Us

_Contact Information and Demographics_

In certain areas of the Sites, such as those in which you complete a profile, submit your resume, create a new account, or enter Dice-sponsored contests or promotions, we may request that you provide us with certain personal information, such as your e-mail address, first and last name, postal zip code, phone number, profession, work experience, social media information, photographs, race and ethnicity, gender, veteran status, citizenship, citizenship status, and/or work eligibility. We may, in such situations, seek to identify which informational items are required and which are optional.

_Education, Professional, and Employment-Related Information_

If you choose to register for job opportunities or apply for a job posted by our customers, we ask for information about your education, employment information and history, job skills, qualifications, titles, and other work-related information that may be relevant to the profile you are creating or the job applications you submit. You also may have the opportunity to submit a resume, curriculum vitae, or other documents you select as relevant to your profile or application.

_Other Information You Submit_

We may also collect any other information you submit when you contact us: this includes any information you provide in a submission through our surveys, Contact Support form, chat functions, or other contact methods.

###### Personal Information We Passively Collect: Device and System Information

When visitors use the Services, we passively collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited, the order in which they were visited, and which links were "clicked". Collecting such information involves the collection and logging of IP addresses, MAC address, operating system, device type, mobile ad identifiers, browsing history, search history and information regarding an individual’s interaction with an internet website, application or advertisement, Internet Service Provider (ISP) and browser software used by each user of the Services. In some instances, we may collect geo-location based information for the purpose of helping identify jobs in your area.

The information we collect helps us identify the most popular areas of the Sites and determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. In addition, we may disclose some of this information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have viewed and/or clicked their advertisements.

On mobile applications, we use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Services on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregate usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from.

On mobile applications, we may send push notifications to your device. You may opt-out of these at the device level.

You may opt out of location-based services by editing the setting at the device level.

###### Searchable Profiles

In the past, job seekers may have elected to make their profile searchable by our customers on a confidential basis only. Dice no longer offers this feature for job seekers, but for those job seekers who had previously registered on this basis, the user's name and contact information will not be displayed to customers performing searches on the Sites. If the customer desires to contact the confidential job seeker regarding an employment opportunity, they will send an email to the job seeker through our system. We will forward the email to the seeker's email address. The seeker's email address will not be provided directly to the customer. When posting a resume confidentially, it is the job seeker's responsibility to ensure that their contact information is not included within their resume attachment.

###### Children and Minors

Dice Services are not available to children under 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16 years of age.

###### California Residents: Personal Information Categories Collected and Sources of that Information

The information we collect, and may have collected in the last twelve (12) months, would include the following categories of personal information under the CCPA:

1. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)), such as name, address, telephone number, education, employment, and employment history (some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories)
2. Identifiers such as your real name, alias, postal address, zip code, telephone number, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers
3. Education information
4. Unique and online identifiers such as device identifiers, internet protocol addresses, cookie identifiers, beacon identifiers, pixel tags or mobile ad identifiers or similar technology, or other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers that can be used to identify a particular consumer or device
5. For representatives or employees of our customers, commercial information that identifies or could reasonably be linked to your organization or you acting on behalf of your organization, such as products or services purchased, obtained, or considered by your organization or you acting on behalf of your organization, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies by your organization or you acting on behalf of your organization
6. Internet or other electronic network activity information that identifies or could reasonably be linked to you, such as browsing history, search history and information regarding an individual’s interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement
7. Professional or employment-related information, such as current or past job history or performance evaluations
8. Location information, such as your precise geolocation while you access our sites or apps if you have enabled location services on your device
9. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law, which may include age if 40 years or older, race, color, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender), veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information)
10. Inferences drawn from personal information, such as person's preferences, characteristics, , abilities, or aptitudes.
11. Information defined as sensitive under the CCPA, including precise geolocation information, racial or ethnic origin and/or immigration status.

We may collect, and may have collected the categories of personal information described above from the sources described in this Information We Gather section, including:

* Directly from you when you provide us information.
* Passively through automatic and indirect means from your devices, including information processed through the means described in the Tracking Technologies section below.
* From third parties, including publicly available sources as described in the Profile Supplementation section below.

###### Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Virginia and Montana: Collection of Personal Information Defined as Sensitive Under Applicable Law Collection

Some of the information we collect may be defined as sensitive under Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Virginia and Montana privacy laws. Such information may include, depending on the state in which you reside, precise geolocation information, racial or ethnic origin, and/or citizenship, citizenship status, or immigration status.

###### Information That Is Publicly Available, Indexed by Search Engines, or Purchased from Third Parties

To provide services to our customers, Dice may collect indexed content, including information about you, from a variety of publicly available websites or search engines. Indexed content may include personal information from sources such as posts on blogs, posts on social media sites, information within social media profiles, and online community platforms. The personal information included in indexed content may consist of contact information and demographics, education, professional, and employment-related information, and other personal information about you on publicly available websites. In general, such indexed content is available through standard search engines or by visiting the public websites themselves. We combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. Dice may append this information to your profile or use this content to create a profile, whether or not an individual has an account with us. If you would like to remove the information we collect, contact us at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Support). Dice has no ownership rights to the indexed content sourced from third-party sites and cannot guarantee that we will not collect information from a publicly available source later.

Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have about you, may include job and industry information, such as skills, title, experience, qualifications, etc. and any other publicly available information such as social profiles.

###### Other Users

Please note that we cannot control the acts of users of the Services. All members and visitors should be aware that, when they disclose personal information in a resume or profile or other medium, the information may be collected and used by others to send that person unsolicited email from other parties outside Dice. In the event that you encounter any Dice user who is improperly collecting or using information about you or other users, please contact [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

**B. How we use the information we gather**

Please take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways we use the information we gather. Dice encourages all third parties involved, including its advertisers, to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and users and to handle personal information responsibly. Nevertheless, in the event you encounter any third party associated with, or who claims association with, Dice who you feel is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

###### How we use passively collected information

We use information collected passively, as identified above, in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful Services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors and users, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Services. We may provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers, users, and other current and potential business partners. We may also use the aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked through links to their sites.

###### How we use personal information

We may use the contact information and demographics, education, professional, and employment information, device and system information, and other personal information you submit or we collect for the following purposes:

1. To understand a user's needs and create content that is relevant to the user, such as by using skills information from your profile to identify relevant job opportunities;
2. To generate statistical studies, such as by aggregating device and system information to identify trends in usage of our products and services ;
3. To conduct market research and planning by sending user surveys, such as by using your contact information to solicit feedback about potential new features, products, and services;
4. To notify user referrals of Dice services, information, or products when a user provides contact information for a potential referral and requests that Dice send information about Dice services, information, or products to referrals;
5. To improve services, information, and products, such as by identifying how frequently website and application features are used from device and system information;
6. To help a user complete a transaction, or provide services or customer support to users and to recipients of Dice products, such as by using your contact information to identify your account to troubleshoot the issue;
7. To communicate with the user, including by using information you provide in requests and other communications such as those you submit through our Contact Us form or chat functions to respond to you, and with recipients of Dice products and services, including by providing contact information and education, professional, and employment-related information in your job applications to employers;
8. To email users about services, information, products and offers from our business partners (and as set forth in section C, How we share information we gather);
9. To personalize the Sites for the user, such as when we use cookies to identify you as a returning user and populate your account information;
10. To notify the user of any changes with the Sites which may affect the user, such as using your contact information to communicate the change to you;
11. To enforce terms of use on the Sites, such as by using contact information to identify problematic conduct and respond to it;
12. To allow the user to purchase products, access services, or otherwise engage in activities the user selects, such as using contact information like your username and password to authenticate your account;
13. To allow us to contact you by phone, email and/or social media. In some cases, this includes text messaging or alerts and carrier charges may apply;
14. To provide, support, and develop our Site, applications, and product or service offerings, such as allowing you to apply for job postings using your contact, demographic, and education, professional, and employment-related information;
15. To create, maintain, customize, service, and secure your account with us, such as by using contact information and education, professional, and employment-related information to create and populate your account profile;
16. To audit our interactions with you, such using device and system information for  counting impressions or verifying the quality and effectiveness of content including ads;
17. To prevent malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and participating in any prosecution or enforcement of laws or agreements meant to prevent or punish such activity, such as by using device and system information to identify such activity and using contact information to identify users engaged in such activity;
18. To maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Site, applications, products and services, databases and other technology assets, and our business, including the detection of security incidents, such a using device and system information to monitor the security of our systems;
19. To debug, identify, or repair errors or effectuate similar functional enhancements, such as by using device and usage information to identify and respond to bugs;
20. To develop, improve, and deliver marketing and advertising, such by reviewing the education, professional, and employment-related information in user profiles to determine areas of interest to our users when developing marketing strategy;
21. For legal and operational compliance purposes, such as monitoring all personal information we collect in assessing whether our operations are effectively implementing this policy;
22. To engage in or enable internal uses, such as research, business analytics, development, audits, account management and security, consistent with our relationship with you, or compatible with the context in which you provided the information, such as using device and usage information for internal research for technology development; and
23.  For any other purpose described to you when collecting your personal information before or at the time of collection.

###### Blogs, Forums, and Survey Results

Usernames, identifications ("IDs"), and email addresses (as well as any additional information that a user may choose to post) may be publicly available on the Sites when a user voluntarily and publicly discloses personal information, such as when a user uses features to send a message to another user, or as part of a message posted to a public forum or a publicly-released software application. Users may not be able to change or remove public postings once posted. Any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from these pages, contact us at [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

With respect to surveys, in the event that responses are publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey. Circumstances under which Dice would publicly disclose information collected from surveys include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the Sites' users, providing data to Dice advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications. Where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where Dice advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, Dice reserves the right to disclose any information provided by users, provided that no personal information identifying a specific user is disclosed. Participation in surveys is at a user's option; Dice does not conduct mandatory surveys.

###### California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Virginia and Montana Residents: Personal Information Sales and Personal Information Use and Disclosure for Targeted or Cross-context Behavioral Advertising

We sell personal information that is publicly available, indexed by search engines, or purchased from third parties, which may indicate certain contact and demographic information and education, professional, and employment-related information, to our customers (i.e., potential employers) in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration. We may share or process personal information for targeted or cross-context behavioral advertising.

###### Additional Information for California Residents Regarding Personal Information Sales

With respect to California residents, in the preceding twelve (12) months we may have “sold” personal information that is publicly available, indexed by search engines, or purchased from third parties. That information may include the following categories of personal information established under the CCPA:

1. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))
2. Identifiers
3. Unique and online identifiers
4. Commercial information
5. Professional or employment-related information
6. Location information
7. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law
8. Inferences drawn from personal information.

We do not have actual knowledge that we sell California Personal Information of consumers under 16 years of age or share the California Personal Information of consumers under the age of 16 for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes.

###### California Residents: Business and Commercial Purposes for Using, Disclosing, or Otherwise Processing Personal Information Categories Established by the CCPA

We may collect, use, disclose, or otherwise process the categories of California Personal Information described in the California Personal Information Collection section above for one or more of the business and commercial purposes described in the How We Use the Information We Gather and How We Share Information We Gather sections of this Privacy Policy.

Consistent with the disclosures of this Privacy Policy, we may collect, use, disclose, or otherwise process personal information defined as sensitive under the CCPA, for purposes other than performing the services or providing the products you request, for security and integrity purposes, short-term transient uses where the relevant information is not disclosed to a third party or used to build a consumer profile, performing services on our behalf, undertaking quality and safety control exercises, and other collection and processing that is not for the purpose of inferring characteristics about you.

###### Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Virginia and Montana Residents: Deidentified Information

We will maintain and use deidentified information that does not constitute personal information in deidentified form and will not attempt to reidentify such deidentified information except to the extent permitted under applicable law. We process personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**C. How we share information we gather**

###### Sharing with Service Providers

Dice may share your personal information with service providers to help us with our business activities. The categories of personal information we share with service providers includes contact information, demographics, education information, professional information, employment-related information, device and system-related information, and information that is publicly available, indexed by search engines, or purchased from third parties. Our service providers process personal information for purposes that align to their role in supplying services to us, such as processing payments, email and social network marketing, offering customer service, or operating a community forum.

If you communicate with us through a chat function on the Site, we may disclose the information submitted through or otherwise collected by the chat function to third party service providers that provide or support our chat function tools and services.

Our service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

###### Sharing with Our Customers

The categories of personal information we share with our customers includes contact information, demographics, education information, professional information, employment-related information, and information that is publicly available, indexed by search engines, or purchased from third parties.

Regarding job applications, Dice will not disclose your profile or resume on our Sites to prospective employers without your consent unless you instruct us otherwise.

Job seekers should post profiles and resumes on our Sites only if they wish such information to be viewed by our customers. At any time, job seekers may elect that their profile and resume not be searchable by our customers by logging into their account and changing the status of their profile or, if that is not possible, they may contact us at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) and we will make the change for them.

###### Sharing for Compliance and Legal Purposes

Dice reserves the right to disclose information submitted by or concerning any Site visitor or user as we reasonably feel is necessary to protect our systems or business. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, court order, government agency or law enforcement requestor other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, investigate fraud, protect your safety or the safety of others, or other like circumstance. We also may disclose such information to third parties: (i) in connection with prevention of fraud, deception, or other malicious activities, (ii) where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, (iii) in situations that may involve violations of our terms of use or other rules, (iv) to protect our rights and the rights and safety of others, and (v) as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or Services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution, or to suspend or terminate your use of the Services in connection with any suspected illegal or infringing activity or if you are in violation of our Terms of Use Agreement or other published guidelines.

The categories of personal information we might share in these circumstances includes contact information, demographics, education information, professional information, employment-related information, device or system information, and information that is publicly available, indexed by search engines, or purchased from third parties. We would limit the disclosure to the type of data reasonably necessary to address the request or legal purpose of the disclosure.

###### Sharing for Corporate Reorganization or Disposition

If Dice is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. Dice reserves the right to assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your personal information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of any portion or all of Dice's or its affiliated entities' assets or stock.

The categories of personal information we might share in these circumstances includes contact information, demographics, education information, professional information, employment-related information, device or system information, and information that is publicly available, indexed by search engines, or purchased from third parties.

###### Sharing at Your Direction

We may disclose personal information to third parties to whom you or your authorized representatives direct us to disclose your personal information.  We may disclose personal information to other parties identified by you when collecting your personal information before or at the time of collection, or to which you separately consented. We would disclose any type of personal information you directed us to share at that time.

###### Framing and Co-Branding

The Sites may utilize framing and masking techniques to make it appear that the user is still on the Site when the user is actually on a third-party website. We also have co-branding relationships with certain partners. In these relationships, you will notice our service platform on our partner's page. In this situation, both parties are collecting your data and both privacy policies govern the data collected. We will not share your data with third parties without your consent in these relationships. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Sites and to read the privacy policies of every website that collects personal information.

###### California Residents: Categories of Personal Information Established by the CCPA Shared with Third Parties within the Past Twelve Months

We may, and in the preceding twelve (12) months, may have disclosed the following categories of personal information established under the CCPA to the categories of third parties listed here:

1. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
2. Identifiers—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
3. Unique and online identifiers—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
4. Commercial information—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
5. Internet or other electronic network activity information—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
6. Professional or employment-related information—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
7. Location information—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
8. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
9. Inferences drawn from personal information—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.
10. Information defined as sensitive under the CCPA, including precise geolocation information—to our service providers, our customers, and to the third parties or for the purposes otherwise described in this How We Share Information We Gather section or Privacy Policy.

You may have the right to request further information about our disclosures, as described below.

**D. Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as cookies, beacons (including pixels), and javascripts are used by Dice and our partners, analytics, and service providers. These technologies are used generally for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and gathering demographic information about our user base.  

Some Internet browsers have a “do-not-track” feature that let you tell the Site that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, the Site does not respond to browser “do-not-track” signals. We allow third parties to use the Site to collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites, applications, and other online products or services.

###### Cookies

We and our partners use cookies on the Sites. A "browser" or "HTTP" cookie is a unique text file that may be used for data analysis, and enables a web site to tailor information presented to a user based on a user's browsing program. Dice may use browser cookies to personalize a user's pages at our Sites, to remember a user when the user registers for products or services, for fraud prevention, advertising, or to track visits to our Sites. If a user does not want Dice or its partners to deploy browser cookies in the user's browser when the user visits the Sites, the user may set the browser to reject cookies or to notify the user when a web site tries to place cookies in the browser program. Rejecting cookies may affect a user's ability to use some of the products, features, functions, or services on our Sites.  To adjust your cookies preferences, please click [here](https://www.dicepilot.com/about/privacy-policy/#cmpscreencustom).

###### Pixels

We use pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These pixels are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable our ad management partner to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Sites. The information that we collect and share does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to [https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/) or you may also opt out by clicking [here](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

###### Web Beacons

From time to time we use web beacons. A web beacon is a string of code that provides a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data, or determining how many times a specific web page has been viewed. Web beacons enable Dice to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits a Site, and to learn which banner ads bring users to each Site. For example, when a user visits a web page, the code for the page may include instructions to go to another server to gather a single pixel graphic image. Web beacons are not placed on a user's computer.

###### Log files

Dice web servers may automatically log aggregate information, such as a user's IP address, domain name, browser type, date and time of access, and other log file data.

###### Advertisements

Any ads appearing on the Sites may be delivered to visitors by third parties, such as Google. For more information about Google’s advertising delivery, please click here: [http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can communicate to advertising delivery providers that participate in the following consumer choice mechanisms by visiting:

1. Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)'s self-regulatory opt-out page ([optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/)) and mobile application-based "AppChoices" download page (https://youradchoices.com/appchoices)
2. Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)'s self-regulatory opt-out page ([optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)).

###### Links to third party web sites

Links to third party web sites or widgets to enable sharing of information through social networks on the Sites are provided solely as a convenience to the user. When a user uses these links, the user leaves the Sites. Dice has not reviewed these third-party sites, does not control, and is not responsible for, any of them, their content or privacy practices. Dice does not endorse or make any representations about the third-party sites, or any information, services, or products found on the sites. If a user decides to access any of the linked sites, Dice encourages the user to read their privacy statements. The user accesses such sites at user's own risk.

**E. Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please help keep your account safe by using a strong password.

If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can contact us at [security@dice.com](mailto:security@dice.com?subject=Security).

**F. Surveys and Sweepstakes**

Occasionally, Dice may conduct surveys in order to better deliver advertisements and content and to better understand your needs relating to the Services. We will not share your survey information with any third-party, except in aggregate form.

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). The sweepstakes rules, to the extent it conflicts with this policy, will govern that particular promotion or sweepstakes - please remember to read it carefully. We may use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor the use of the Sites, to personalize the Sites, to send participants an email, and to measure participants' demographics, interests and opinions. We may use a third-party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personal information for any other purpose. We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

###### Referrals

If you choose to use our referral service to tell another person about a job, we will ask you for that person's email address. We will automatically send that person a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We use this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, and do not store these email addresses.

**G. Social Media Features**

The Sites include social media features, such as social media link outs and widgets that run on our Sites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**H. Data Subject Rights and Correction of Personal Information**

At any time, you can request from Dice information about which personal data Dice processes about you and the correction or deletion of such personal data. If your information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update, amend, and delete/remove your personal information or deactivate your account by making the change on your account page, by emailing our Customer Support at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Support) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

Depending on which laws apply to your personal information, we may only be able to do some of these actions for you. If you request an action and we refuse to do it, we will explain your legal rights, the reason for our refusal and any recourse you may have. Please note that if you request that Dice delete your personal data, you will no longer be able to use any Dice service that requires the use of your personal data. If you have provided more than one email address to our service, you may continue to be contacted, unless you request to unsubscribe each email address you have provided.

If Dice uses your personal data based on your consent or to perform a contract with you, you may further request from Dice a copy of the personal data that you have provided to Dice. For all individuals located outside of California, please contact [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) and specify the information or processing activities to which your request relates, the format in which you would like this information, and whether the personal data is to be sent to you or another recipient.

We will respond to your request without undue delay within 30 days. Dice reserves the right to take reasonable steps to verify customer identity prior to granting access or processing changes or corrections. Please direct any such request to [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

###### Retention of Your Personal Information

1. Data Retention**.** We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you Services, contact us at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Support). You can also delete your account via your profile dashboard. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
2. Blogs: The Sites may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Support). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
3. Testimonial. We post testimonials on the Sites which may contain personal information. Prior to posting a testimonial, we do obtain consent by email (or a release agreement) which includes the person’s consent to publish their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Support).
4. Email preferences. You may sign up to receive emails or other communications from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the "Unsubscribe" link found in emails we send you, by making a change on your account page, or by contacting us at [support@dice.com](mailto:support@dice.com?subject=Support).

###### California Residents: Information Access  

If you are a resident of California, you have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information during the applicable period of time for your request. To do so, you must first submit a verifiable request pursuant to the California Residents: Exercising Privacy Rights section below. 

You may be entitled to receive:

* The categories of personal information established by the CCPA we collected about you.
* The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting personal information about you, selling personal information about you.
* If we sell your personal information or disclose your personal information for a business purpose, a list of the categories of third parties to whom we sold personal information or disclosed personal information for a business purpose, as applicable, identifying the categories of personal information established by the CCPA sold, shared, or disclosed to those parties during the applicable period of time for your request.
* The categories of third parties with whom we disclose personal information generally.
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.

###### California Residents: Data Portability

If you are a resident of California, you may request to receive a copy of your personal information in a readily usable format to the extent technically feasible.

###### California Residents: Deletion Request Rights

Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we delete the personal information that we collected about you. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.

Bases for denying your deletion requests include circumstances where retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) to:

* Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you.
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
* Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.).
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent.
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us.
* Comply with a legal obligation.
* Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

###### California Residents: Right to Correct Inaccuracies

If you are a California resident, you may request that we correct personal information about you that is inaccurate. We will take into account the nature of the personal information and the purposes of our processing when we address your request.

###### California Residents: Right to Opt Out of Sales

If you are a California resident, you have the right to opt out of our sale of your personal information. We require certain contact information, such as your name and email address, to opt you out of sales of your personal information. You may submit that information and request to exercise your opt out right by visiting our opt out mechanism at [https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor).

You may use opt-out preference signals, which communicate opt-out preferences based on your browser or device identifier, on the Site. The personal information we sell is not linked to your browser or device identifier so opt-out preference signals will not have an effect on any sales of your personal information. Please submit an opt-out request through the following link if you would like to opt out of sales: [https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor). We do not charge a fee or require any valuable consideration if you use an opt-out preference signal, change your experience with our products or services based on your opt out preference signal, or display notifications, pop-ups, or other interstitial content in response to your opt-out preference signal.

###### California Residents: Right to Non-discrimination

Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising your access, data portability, and deletion rights described above.

###### California Residents: Exercising Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may exercise the rights described above using the links provided above as applicable or submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either calling us at [1-888-321-3423](tel:1-888-321-3423) or visiting and completing our [webform](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor)

You may designate someone to submit requests and act on your behalf as an authorized agent. We may mandate additional requirements for requests submitted through an authorized agent, such as requiring you to verify your identity directly with us or to directly confirm the authorized agent’s permission to act on your behalf.

Your request must provide information sufficient to permit us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or an authorized representative of that person. Your request also must include enough detail for us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. In order to verify your request, we may ask you to provide information such as your name, street address, city, state, zip code, and e-mail address or phone. If we are not able to verify your request, we may contact you for more information. If we are unable to verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you, we may not be able to respond to your request.

###### Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Oregon, Texas, Virginia and Montana Residents: Additional Privacy Rights

Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Oregon, Texas, Virginia and Montana privacy laws provide residents of those states with additional rights regarding our use of their personal information subject to those laws. We have described such privacy rights below as applicable. 

As the rights described below are provided by law, there may be limitations or exceptions that apply to your request in accordance with applicable legal requirements. We have described these rights generally, without noting all applicable or potentially applicable limitations or exceptions. When you make a request, we may provide more detailed information regarding any legal requirements applicable to or your request and whether any exception or limitation applies. 

Subject to certain limitations and exceptions, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Oregon, Texas, Virginia and Montana provide residents of those states with rights to:

* Confirm whether we process their personal information.
* Access personal information we have collected about them.
* Delete personal information.
* Receive a copy of their personal information in a portable, and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. 
* Opt-out of personal data sales by visiting our opt out mechanism at [https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor) and completing a submission through that link.

Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia and Montana also provide their states’ residents with a right to correct inaccuracies in their personal information, taking into account the information’s nature and purposes for processing.

Oregon also provides its residents with a right to obtain additional information regarding the third parties to whom we disclosed their personal information.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us by visiting our [webform](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor) and completing the fields, or through a method described in the “Questions?” section below and identifying the exercise of one of your privacy rights as the reason you are contacting us, or as specifically described elsewhere in this section. To appeal a decision regarding a request to exercise these rights, please describe the issue and request an appeal by responding to the communication of our decision, using our [webform](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor), or otherwise contacting us as described in the “Questions?” section below.

###### Colorado Residents: Additional Privacy Rights Information

If you are a Colorado resident, you may authorize another person, acting on your behalf, to submit privacy rights requests on your behalf. Your authorized agent may submit the request using the webform or the methods described in the “Questions?” section below. You may also use an authorized agent to opt out of exchanges of your personal information for money or other valuable consideration using our opt-out link above or  through opt-out preference signals. We will respect an opt-out request received from a person authorized by the consumer to act on your behalf if we can authenticate, with commercially reasonable effort, your identity and the authorized agent's authority to act on your behalf

We may use commercially reasonable processes to authenticate your identity or the authority of your authorized agent. Those processes will consider the privacy right you seek to exercise, the type, sensitivity, value, and volume of relevant personal information, the level of harm improper access or use could cause, and the cost of authentication. In order to authenticate your request, we may require you to provide information to enable us to match that information to the records we maintain. The information we request for authentication purposes may include your name, email address, phone number, or other information that may allow us to authenticate your identity.  We may mandate additional requirements for requests submitted through an authorized agent, such as requiring you to verify your identity directly with us or to directly confirm the authorized agent’s permission to act on your behalf.

You may use opt-out preference signals, which communicate opt-out preferences based on your browser or device identifier, on the Site. The personal information we sell is not linked to your browser or device identifier so opt-out preference signals will not have an effect on any sales of your personal information. Please submit an opt-out request through the following link if you would like to opt out of sales: [https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor](https://www.dice.com/about/ccpa#ccpa-form-anchor).

###### Texas Residents:  Additional Information Data Broker Information

The entity maintaining this website is a data broker under Texas law.  To conduct business in Texas, a data broker must register with the Texas Secretary of State (Texas SOS).  Information about data broker registrants is available on the Texas SOS website.

**I. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Note that, by using the Services, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Services. Your continued use of the Services following changes to this Policy will mean you accept the changes; therefore, please bookmark this page and review it periodically. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or any other privacy issues in connection with the Services, please e-mail us at [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

**J. Questions?**

Questions and complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [privacy@dice.com](mailto:privacy@dice.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). We commit to investigating and resolving complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. You may also contact us by telephone (+1) 888-321-3423, or by mail.

Legal Department, Data Protection Officer  
Dice Inc.,  
5745 Raccoon River Drive, Suite 200

West Des Moines, IA 50266  
USA

To help us address the issue effectively, please provide the following:

* The specific data privacy complaint (please provide as much detail as possible including country, your understanding of the data privacy infringement and issues, redress requested);
* Your full name and how we can contact you; and
* Any previous correspondence on this specific data privacy issue.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Loading...
